[♪ tense music playing]
[mercenary]
No bio-signals detected inside.
[scanner beeping]
[♪ tense music continues]
If Jeong Jinman is actually here…
then I'll gouge out my other eye.
Whether he's here or not,
we stay the course of action.
That's the reason we lost him
in the first place.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
This is where you holed up
and lived the good life, is that it?
You sly dog.
I would bet that Jinman…
is watching us from somewhere out there.
[mercenary]
Secret passage found in the bathroom.
There's a secret passage.
[robot feet thumping]
[device beeping]
[devices beeping rapidly]
Pull out now!
[beeping speeds up]
[♪ suspenseful music builds]
[explosion]
[shrapnel scatters]
[sighs]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Jinwoo] It's bulletproof.
It won't break at this range.
[sighs]
Let's pull back.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
STYLE
::cue()
EPISODE 02
RECLUSE
[Jian panting]
1 YEAR LATER
[Jinman] You can blame me for all of it.
[sighs]
I couldn't lose you too, Jian.
That's why the shop was created.
To protect you.
You know, I knew
you weren't ordinary, Uncle.
But isn't this insane?
You're saying to protect me,
you took money and sold guns
to mercenaries and assassins.
You're an arms dealer, right?
That means the weapons
that you sell to those people…
are used to kill, aren't they?
[Jinman] Mm-hmm.
This is my world, Jeong Jian.
Where you have to kill
if you wanna stay alive.
I did the best I could
to keep you out of danger…
but it found you anyway,
and that's my fault.
[scoffs]
[shuddering breath]
[♪ tense music playing]
I don't need an apology anymore.
-Take care of yourself, Jeong Jinman.
-Listen up, Jeong Jian.
Whatever happens,
the safest place for you is with me.
Uncle, I don't want anything
to do with this world.
You may not wanna hear this, but…
[sighs]
-you're already in it.
-But that can change.
I thought you died
and now you're sitting here.
None of this has anything to do with me.
You said so yourself.
Whatever I decide to do,
it's my choice, right?
These are yours.
Jeong Jian, from now on,
you have to make it on your own.
SOCIAL SECURITY CARD
LEE ARIN
[♪ tense music continues]
[Jian] One day…
in the future, when everything is settled…
and I can return to a normal life…
I'll come back.
[panting]
[Brother] Jeong Jian.
Here, just in case, you should take this.
STYLE
::cue()
If anything happens,
u-use it to contact me.
And this, this is for… security.
It should help.
And also this bag here, just…
Once you get somewhere safe,
open it when you're alone.
-Hey…
-Hm?
If you and my uncle install cameras
and bug my place, you're dead.
Okay, okay.
I swear. I won't do that, I… I swear.
[♪ soft music playing]
Take care.
Jeong Jian, you too.
[♪ determined tense music playing]
[♪ music fades]
[Jian panting]
[gate rattles]
[door lock clicks]
[Seongjo] You gonna keep running
under the moon every night? Huh?
Will you look at that,
our little Jian's pretending
she can't hear me, but she does.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Jian breathes shakily]
Thanks to a certain someone,
I've got an itch on my neck
that I can't seem to scratch.
Can you help me?
[♪ eerie music playing]
-[head thumps]
-[Jian gasps]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[seagulls squawking]
[store owner]
Come get your tofu! Fresh chilies!
Tasty garlic!
Get some tomatoes. Cherry tomatoes.
Green onions. Green onions here!
Hey, come on, what are you checking
inside the bag for, huh?
-[sighs]
-I'm hardly making squat.
Come here for a sec.
Look, Grandma Pilsun
ordered shiitakes, right?
So why'd you get
oyster mushrooms then, huh?
Ah, Woojin, shiitake or oyster,
it's all the same.
These are actually better for you.
And shiitakes are so expensive now.
What's price got to do with it?
You think Hanam-do folk can't pay?
Last time you pulled this,
those grandmas kicked ass hard.
You wanna go through that again?
Keep this up and your store
will stop getting business here.
Ah, Woojin, Woojin!
Hey, why are you doing this, man?
We've known each other
for a while now, right?
Hey, are you lonely?
You want me to set you up? Huh?
[groans] Stop speaking nonsense.
[elder 1] I mean, he's just sitting
around, waiting for who knows what.
What's there for him to do
besides eat three meals and sleep?
[elders laughing]
Arin, are you in some kind of a rush?
You know you can slow down a little.
-Hey, Arin!
-Yes?
We're hourly, girl. Hourly, yeah?
All of us are paid by the hour.
We have to take it slow,
so we can make more money.
You can't rush everything on your own.
Right.
I can't tell if this girl's not listening
or just doesn't understand
what I'm saying.
[elder 2] All right, that's enough.
I think I'm all finished here.
Please take your time. I'll be going now.
What? What did I say?
She walks off like that,
then I'm the bad guy here, is that it?
Has it already been a year
since that girl got here?
It hasn't been a year yet.
It's just that I don't get along with her,
I really can't.
And when I try to start a conversation,
she barely says a word.
That girl!
I don't like anything about her.
Is she still running in the middle
of the night like a bat out of hell?
-That's what I heard.
-Come on, ladies, let it go.
-Oh, my sonny's here. [chuckles]
-How many times I gotta say it?
How's it going?
Ladies, listen,
we have to include Ms. Arin
because that makes 30 of us.
We're getting federal support.
They'll stop the payments to everyone
if she leaves us now.
And young folks these days expect
to be treated with a little respect, yeah?
It's just that we're trying really hard
with her every day.
And why are you being mean to us for?
She's the one with the nasty attitude,
isn't she?
Oh, my gosh. I can't understand
why you're taking her side.
[chuckles] Why do you think?
Woojin isn't a little boy anymore.
He's gotta start thinking about marriage.
-[elders laughing]
-God!
Hey, quit trying to set us up like that.
I've got my hands full
taking care of you all.
I mean, marriage is the furthest thing
I can think of.
[elder 3] Well, you should.
-Hey, um, Mrs. Pilsun. Uh…
-Huh?
They were out of shiitake,
so they got oyster mushrooms.
You're kidding. What?
[Pilsun] Shiitakes and
oyster mushrooms are totally different.
That general-store fraud!
He gets low-quality junk
and just… just pockets the cash, right?
Don't worry about it. It's handled. Yeah?
All right, ladies, I'll drop them off
in front of the house, okay?
Take yours when you head home.
-[elder 2] Yeah. Thank you.
-[elder 4] Okay, sounds good.
Meongejeon? Still got some left.
I appreciate it, though.
-Thank you.
-It's not meant for you.
Take it and give it to Arin.
I was actually thinking of giving it
to her later today,
but the damn girl just took off like that.
When you go to see her,
you should give it to her real casually
and say, "Wanna sit down and eat together?
Just you and me?"
-[elders laugh]
-Ah, forget it. Cut it out. Jeez!
STYLE
::cue()
I really can't do this, you ladies.
I really can't!
[elder 2] You look homeless.
-[Woojin] I'll see you later.
-[elder 1] Okay, Romeo!
Ms. Arin, would you like
to have some of this?
[sighs]
That's not it.
Arin, Arin, I… [mumbles] I… I…
I was wondering, have you eaten yet?
[♪ cheeky music playing]
Arin, I was just…
[button clicks]
[sighs]
[♪ cheeky music continues]
Are you there?
Ms. Arin?
You there, Ms. Arin?
Are you in there?
What is that?
What's going on here?
[Jian whimpering]
HANNIBAL: THE CONQUEROR OF ROME
[Woojin] Ms. Arin?
Are you home?
[yelps]
What was that?
-[Woojin] Ms. Arin, are you okay?
-[gasps]
-[snare clanks]
-Huh?
-[whirring]
-[Woojin yelping, screaming]
[clattering]
[Woojin whimpering, groaning]
[groaning in pain]
What is this? What are you doing here?
That's… Okay, what happened is that…
that Granny Jeomrye told me
to take this to you.
Uh, c-could you just…? [sighs]
[Woojin panting]
[groans]
I'm sorry about this.
I shouldn't be hopping the fence
without asking.
Can I…
ask why it's…?
Never mind.
[gate opens, closes]
[Woojin] Right on my ass.
[♪ tense music playing]
[keypad beeping]
[lock clicks open]
[lock clicks shut]
[♪ tense music continues]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ music ends]
[indistinct lively chatter]
[phone buzzing]
DIRECTOR LEE YONGHAN
MADE CONTACT?
-[staff] Are you Attorney Jang Inseop?
-Who's asking?
-I'll take that.
-[Inseop] No, it's fine.
-I'll take it, it's for me.
-Sir.
Go ahead. This is Jang Inseop.
[Jinman] This is Jeong Jinman.
Yeah.
I heard you were a man of his word,
that's why I'm confused
you're not here at our meeting.
[Jinman] I think we both know
you went back on your word first.
Is that right?
I don't understand what you mean.
I've been here since 2:30.
[phone buzzing]
[Jinman] Check your phone.
KIM CHANWOO
AFFILIATION: BABYLON, MERCENARY TEAM 1
PARK CHEOLMIN
JEONG HYEONSOO
AFFILIATION: BABYLON, MERCENARY TEAM 1
[♪ uneasy music playing]
[sighs] Yes. [clears throat]
Yeah, I understand what you're saying.
However, as you know,
our employees' information is classified.
It seems that you've breached our servers.
That's a whole other negotiation,
I'm afraid.
[phone buzzing]
CONFIDENTIAL
ASSASSINATION OPERATION
OF APPOINTED PRIME MINISTER OF CAMBODIA
Uh…
Yes, I'm understanding exactly
what you're…
What you're implying with this message.
[Jinman] Once I'm convinced that Babylon
is genuinely willing to negotiate with me,
I'll contact you again.
We're done. Let's head back.
How do you think he found out?
If I knew that,
you think I would've been flustered?
[car beeps]
Wait a second.
Uh…
-I was gonna get the car washed.
-Sir?
You should probably take the bus back.
It'll take a while.
No, that's fine, sir.
I can go along and keep you company.
No, it's all right. Just go.
-It's really fine with me.
-I said, just go on.
Right. I'll see you back there, sir.
[sighs]
[♪ low tense music playing]
[Jinman] Let's go.
STYLE
::cue()
Where… where do you…? I mean…
Weren't you going to the car wash?
I didn't know agents would be there.
I swear. I wasn't briefed on it. Honestly.
[Jinman] Yes, I'm aware.
I already know who ordered it.
[Inseop] Even so,
you shouldn't have breached our server.
That was the only way I could have
handled this negotiation here.
[sighs] So, all right, why don't you
just tell me what you want.
My conditions are simple.
A permanent ceasefire.
Going forward, Jeong Jian, as well
as anyone I've ever associated with,
will now be off-limits.
If they honor this,
the contents of the server
will never see the light of day.
Once I'm convinced that Babylon
will keep their end of the deal…
I will return the server.
However, if anyone so much
as touches a hair on my niece's head,
or if she gets even the tiniest scratch,
Babylon's true nature will be exposed
to the world.
If I find any suspicious men
lurking around my niece,
or if her phone just happens
to stop working for whatever reason,
Babylon's true nature will be made public.
These are my non-negotiables.
That seems straightforward,
but I don't know
if negotiations will be possible.
I'll make the first move
to open the conversation.
How exactly?
First, I will convert Murthehelp
to an indefinite shutdown state.
I will halt all transactions
and activities
between the codes immediately.
I'll be watching.
Congratulations to you and your wife
on your 15-month-old child,
Legal Team Attorney Jang Inseop.
DEPART ON SIGNAL
Wait, that's…
Then, for now…
[sighs]
[helicopter whirs]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Jinman didn't say anything else?
No, he just stated his terms
and disappeared quietly.
It feels like he's got Babylon
right where he wants it.
What should we do?
Is Jinman still an active target?
[staff 1] …orders were to…
What are you doing here?
[security] Get the hell out of here.
[staff 1] What are you saying?
I said, move it!
[security] This doesn't concern you. Move.
Step aside. Step aside now!
What's going on here?
We haven't met before, have we?
I am Kusanagi Jin.
Regional Head of Babylon East Asia.
Despite the name, I'm Korean.
But I never really lived here.
STYLE
::cue()
[immigration officer] Okay.
IDENTITY CHECKLIST
FOR IMMIGRATION OFFICERS
Um… Uh…
-What time do you finish?
-In five hours.
We will finish after and…
after five hours, we go out.
Five hours afterwards come back.
You understand?
-Okay, yeah. Yeah.
-Okay?
-Move, move. Move.
-Okay.
[worker] Hey.
-[metal clanking]
-[seagulls squawking]
[♪ cool intriguing music playing]
-[engine revs]
-[tires screech]
[♪ cool intriguing music intensifies]
[♪ music stops]
Yes.
I'll take full responsibility
and step down.
However…
before I resign…
I would like to be the one to finish it.
Jeong Jinman served under me
for ten years.
Not a single soul knows Jeong Jinman
better than I do.
Please let me be the one--
I believe I have already given you
more than a year
to wrap this mess up.
Am I wrong?
[sighs]
It's been a year since Babylon's had
a functioning Korean branch.
We haven't been able
to deploy any covert operations,
officials are hesitant to use us,
and as a result,
revenue has been cut in half.
[laughs]
No matter what Jeong Jinman's notoriety
is within our circles,
the rumor that Babylon was taken down
by a single ex-mercenary…
Let's just say our credibility's damaged.
If that wasn't enough,
Babylon's top secret intel could
get leaked at any time, right?
We gave you an entire year
to clean this matter up and you couldn't.
That tells me everything I need to know.
The decision's already been made.
You're released of your duties here.
Babylon's no longer your home.
[♪ slow tense music playing]
[BABYLON INTERNAL CONFIDENTIALITY
AGREEMENT]
[security] What are you doing here?
Turn around. I said, turn arou--
-[punches land]
-[groans]
Hey! What the hell are you--
[clanging]
[body thuds]
[groaning in pain]
You're in someone else's country.
Don't you have any manners?
[in Japanese] This damn country…
gets emotional about everything.
[in English] Say hello, Bale.
She's your direct superior.
[Bale] What are you doing?
Weren't you gonna get Jinman?
And what are they doing here?
[♪ low menacing music playing]
And you are…
Bale?
Orders from above are
to capture Jeong Jinman.
That's what I'm doing here.
[♪ electronic music playing]
[♪ music stops]
STYLE
::cue()
BABYLON DIRECTOR LEE YONGHAN
[♪ low suspenseful music playing]
[phone buzzing]
SON
[coughs, clears throat]
-Ah. Hey.
-[kid] Grandpa!
There you are. How's my little guy, huh?
[son] I was telling him
how I wanted to hear your voice.
-[Yonghan laughing]
-[kid] Grandpa, when are we
gonna play catch?
[son] You need to brush your teeth
and get ready for bed.
[Yonghan] All right, Sanggyu.
-[Sanggyu] Yeah?
-It's so late.
-[kid] No fair!
-Put him to bed already.
-[Sanggyu] Right.
-[kid] You made a promise.
Hey, kid.
That's what moms are like, all right?
[Sanggyu] I already told her
we had a lot of kimchi left.
But she won't have it,
she insists on bringing some by.
I know it's harder for her
to make the trip these days.
I just worry about her, that's all.
[♪ electronic music playing
through headphones]
Are you there?
Listen, son, quit your complaining.
Treat your mom well while she's around.
That goes for your wife
and my grandson too.
[Sanggyu] Dad, is everything all right?
Of course, everything's fine.
See you.
[♪ electronic music continues
through headphones]
[thuds]
-[gunshot]
-[♪ electronic music playing]
-[both grunting]
-[gunshot]
[grunts]
[yelps, groans]
[panting]
[groaning]
[♪ music stops]
[breathes raggedly in shock]
-[grunts in pain]
-[body thuds]
[♪ electronic music continues
through headphones]
[clanging]
-[elevator chimes]
-[elevator door opens]
The address is Yuseong-gu…
[♪ electronic music playing
through headphones]
[engine revving]
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight…
What the hell? We're missing a guy.
Huh?
Hey!
Look. We're… There's a person missing.
-[immigration officer] Where is he, huh?
-[navigator] That guy,
earlier, he said he's going to toilet.
-Maybe he shit.
-Hey!
That's no excuse. Know what?
-You better find him quickly and--
-Sorry, sorry, sorry. Uh…
Toilet. Uh…
Diarrhea.
Korean food is too spicy.
[beeps]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[phone line ringing]
[phone buzzing]
[chuckles]
Mission successful.
Okay, job well done.
Take some time off
until your next mission.
[co-leader] I miss you. You liking Korea?
Not at all.
The office interior is tacky as hell.
I need to relocate.
[co-leader]
Okay. I'll let you get back to it.
Mm-hmm.
MURTHEHELP - THIS WEBSITE IS
CURRENTLY UNDER CONSTRUCTION.
[Jian yelps]
[seagulls squawking]
Hey, Arin!
Oh. Hi, aunties.
-Are you going?
-Going where?
[Jeomrye] What do you mean?
Once a month, folks from the island head
to the mainland to have a feast together.
You didn't know?
Ah…
We eat some tasty food,
sing songs together, play some games.
-Come with us.
-[Pilsun] Jeez, why would youngsters
wanna hang around
with a bunch of old folks?
What are your plans for the day?
My phone broke, so I was heading
to Sacheon for a new one.
[Woojin] Hi, ladies.
[elders] Ooh!
Together?
[humming merrily]
Hey, while we're out,
have sonny here show you a good time.
[Jeomrye] Come on. Hey, come on!
[elder] Nothing more than hand-holding.
It's your… first time off the island,
isn't it?
Since you moved to Hanam-do, right?
Yes.
Uh, you should know,
the Sacheon boat over there comes and goes
whenever it seemingly wants to.
It'll stay put right there
if there's no waves at all,
not to mention their schedule.
Hm.
Uh, if the ship doesn't go out
or you don't get on board, give me a call.
I can take my boat out there.
Uh…
That's just what everyone around here
does already.
It's totally fine, so please feel free
to call if you want.
Oh.
-That's--
-I appreciate it.
Wait! My number's really easy. Here.
0070-1004.
007. Bang! 1004.
You can remember it like that.
Yeah. Really appreciate it.
-I better get on the boat now, so…
-Yeah.
[Woojin] Safe travels.
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
You idiot.
PHONES FOR ALL
BUS
[♪ gentle music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[lively chatter]
[sighs]
THAI SPECIALTY RESTAURANT
[owner, in Thai] Welcome.
[Jian, in English] One pad thai, please.
[owner] Of course. This way, please.
[♪ gentle music continues]
[indistinct Thai chatter]
[♪ music turns eerie]
[in English] Jian, you're here
'cause you thought of Pasin, huh?
Yeah.
Oh.
Should've taken a hatchet
to his fucking neck.
-[door opens]
-[store bell chimes]
-[in Thai] Hi, how have you been?
-Welcome.
[indistinct Thai chatter]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[rain pattering]
[both grunt]
[♪ intense music playing]
[in English] Who are you?
Why are you following me?
You left your cell phone in there.
You've been following me since the bus.
I was gonna eat there.
My friend owns that restaurant. [grunts]
[both panting]
[thuds]
[Seongjo cackling]
Do you recall what I said that night?
That I want to recruit you,
that I want to bring you on.
Wow…
You take after your uncle.
You're a born warrior. Warrior.
Fuck off.
[♪ tense music playing]
[♪ music ends]
-[rain pattering]
-[thunder rumbling]
STYLE
::cue()
What?
Are you saying there's no more rides
back to Hanam-do today?
Sorry, they've all been canceled.
These ferries can't go out
in this weather.
[sighs]
[staff 1] What are you doing when you
get off? Have any plans?
[staff 2] No, I don't.
-[staff 1] Going straight home?
-[staff 2] I really should.
[Woojin] Uh, if the ship doesn't go out
or you don't get onboard, give me a call.
My number's really easy. Here.
[boat engine revving]
WOOJIN
[Woojin] Have you had dinner?
What?
Have you had dinner yet?
I haven't. Not yet.
Here, eat this.
You'll get sick on an empty stomach.
That right there is
a Sacheon local delicacy.
It even appeared on YouTube.
It's really amazing.
Thank you so much.
[bottles clink]
Have it with this, it's killer.
[♪ gentle music playing]
Are you gonna ask me about it?
What?
Why I had all that stuff in my yard.
I mean, I would've asked if I were you.
[Woojin] Oh. Oh, that?
Well, everyone's got
their own circumstances in life, right?
I figured it really wasn't my business.
I don't want to overcomplicate things.
Anyhow, the aunties,
they don't mean anything by it either.
They're just trying to get close to you
in their own way,
so don't let them get to you.
-[alarm blaring]
-[coast guard] This is the Coast Guard!
We're conducting a contraband inspection.
Please cooperate.
That you, Woojin?
Stop the boat. Let me take a quick look.
Yes, I understand.
-[engine shuts off]
-Shit. What do I do?
Hey, Arin. One second.
-Could you hold this for a minute, please?
-What?
Shit.
[Woojin grunting]
[strained groaning]
-[Woojin yelps]
-[clattering]
[gasps]
[♪ ominous music playing]
Shit. Shit.
[phone buzzing]
MURTHEHELP
WHEN CAN THE PACKAGE BE RECEIVED?
[♪ ominous music continues]
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
Why is it taking so long?
[sighs]
Look, among all of these classified
servers, there's only three real ones.
No, I get that, but you said
you're the one who made this.
Hey, it's not like I created the fake ones
and put them in there, all right?
Your Kim II Sung University degree
really ain't worth shit, is it?
[Brother]
Sir, sir, sir, Jinman! Sir, sir, sir.
[panting]
Here, here, here, quick, quick, quick.
What is it?
LOOKING FOR A PERSON
$2,000,000 DOLLAR / CASH
NAME: JEONG JIAN
[♪ closing theme music playing]
BASED ON THE NOVEL
BY KANG JI YOUNG